Rate-of-Change Needed to Achieve World-Class Status
Welcome this session on benchmarking.
Now what we’re going to do is explore the rate of change.
And I want to say that's the rate of change of something.
Now, here's the question,
given the automobile average is about Four Sigma, somewhere in there.
How long will it take to achieve Six Sigma?
How long is it going to take to go from Four Sigma to Six Sigma?
That's the question. Well, let’s take a look.
If we improve at a rate
of 25% per year. In other words, if we reduce our defects
by 25% per year.
Then it looks like we’re going to wind up reaching in 27 years, Six Sigma.
That's if we improve 25% per year. That's what this graph’s telling me.
If I improve at 10% per year, we’ll see Six Sigma automobiles in 71 years.
I’d like to see more of a 50% rate of improvement.
At a 50% rate of improvement we’ll get to Six Sigma in one decade.
Is a decade fast enough to reach out in front of your competitors?
That's an interesting question. At a 75% rate, it'll take six years
to reach Six Sigma from where they're at right now in the automobile industry.
How long will it take the medical industry to reach Six Sigma. How many years?
How many years will it take you to reach Six Sigma for the CTQ’s of your life.
Another form of benchmarking.